everpix.com 2013-03-12

# Everpix - Privacy

33cube, Inc. ("33cube") operates the 33cu.be and everpix.com websites as well as the Everpix applications. It is 33cube policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites and applications.

## Gathering of User Data From Everpix Users and Visitors

In connection with your use of the Everpix services, we collect certain non-personally-identifying information as well as personally-identifying information about you, including the following:

  * User data from users who have created an Everpix account: 
    * Account information (email, password, full name),
    * Photos (i.e. the actual images),
    * Metadata (i.e. the metadata retrieved along with or extracted from the photos),
    * Photo collection statistics (e.g. number of photos, origin of photos, camera used...),
    * Usage statistics of our websites and applications.
  * Additional user data from users who have a subscription plan paid through the Everpix website: 
    * Billing full name and address as entered during the payment process
  * User data from visitors: 
    * Usage statistics of our websites and applications.

The collection of this information is intended for 33cube to provide the Everpix services and better understand and serve the users and visitors of our websites and applications.

33cube does discloses a user’s personally-identifying information to other users and personally-identifying information to third parties, only as described below.

## Protection of User Photos and Associated Metadata

Except as otherwise provided below, a user's photos and associated metadata is deemed private to that user, and is not made available to other users or to visitors of the Everpix services.

A user may choose to make available his or her photos, associated metadata, or other personally-identifying information, to other users of the Everpix services, and in such case, 33cube may share such information as authorized by the user through the Everpix services.

A user may also choose to make available such information by explicitly making the information public, or publishing it to third party services such as Facebook or Twitter. In such case, 33cube may so share the information, and the subsequent use of such information will be subject to the terms of such third party services, as applicable.

## Protection of Other Personally-Identifying Information

33cube discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees and its contractors that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 33cube’s behalf, to perform technical services related to the site or applications, or to provide services available at 33cube’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Wherever practical, 33cube will disclose anonymized data instead of personally-identifying information for such purposes, and will restrict the amount of data disclosed appropriately. 33cube will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees and contractors, as described above, 33cube discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when 33cube believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 33cube, third parties or the public at large.

33cube may also disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to a buyer in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or any other form of sale of some or all of 33cube’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by 33cube about its customers is among the assets transferred.

33cube takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Aggregated Statistics

33cube may collect metadata and statistics about the behavior of visitors of its websites and users of its applications. 33cube may display this information publicly or provide it to others, provided that such information is provided in an aggregated and anonymized fashion. However, 33cube does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described above.

## Communications With You

If you have created an Everpix account and have supplied your email address, 33cube may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 33cube and our products. We would however keep this type of emails to a minimum.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 33cube may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 33cube’s sole discretion. 33cube encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Last updated 2013-02-14
